A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Administration, Comptroller, Program Management Cost Files FA501
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program Management Costs, 1961-1984; III
  - E and R -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - E and R -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-983), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - E and R -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-984), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - E and R/HER -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - E and R/PE -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - E and R/SP -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - HA -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - HA -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-981), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - HA -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - HA -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-984) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1971 Logistic Support (Project Staff) and Small Program Actions (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1970 Program Advisory Staff (PA 71-981), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1971 Consultants (PA 71-982), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1971 Training Associates (PA 71-983), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs, Logistic Support, Small Program Actions (PA 71-984), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs, Logistic Support, Small Program Actions (PA 71-985), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1971 Operating Expenses and Small Program Actions, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1971 Logistic Support (Project Staff) and Small Program Actions (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1971 Program Advisory Staff (PA 71-981), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1971 Consultants (PA 71-982), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1971 Training Associates (PA 71-983), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs, Logistic Support, Small Program Actions (PA 71-984), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs, Logistic Support, Small Program Actions (PA 71-985), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1971 Logistic Support and Small Program Actions, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-981), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-984), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-981), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-983), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 70-984), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-984), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-983), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-984), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-981), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-984), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - PB -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-980), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - PB -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-981), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - PB -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs (PA 71-982) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - PB -- FY 1971 Program Management Costs, Appropriations, Fiscal Status Report (PA 71-984), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - PB -- FY 1971 Travel and Study Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1972 General Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1972 General Management Costs (PA 72-981), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1972 General Management Costs (PA 72-982), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1972 General Management Costs, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - E and R -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - E and R -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-981), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - E and R -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-982), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - E and R -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-984), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - E and R -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - HA -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - HA -- FY 1972 Program Advisory Staff (PA 72-981), 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - HA -- FY 1972 Office Expenses (PA 72-984), 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - HA -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1972 Program Advisory Staff (PA 72-981), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1972 Training Associates (PA 72-983), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1972 Office Expenses (PA 72-984), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1972 Logistic Support (PA 72-985), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1972 Consultants (PA 72-982), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1972 Logistic Support (Project Staff) and Small Program Actions (PA 72-980), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1972 Program Advisory Staff (PA 72-981), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1972 Training Associates (PA 72-983), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1972 Office Expenses (PA 72-984), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1972 Logistic Support (PA 72-985), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-981), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-982), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-984), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-981), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-984), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-983), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-984), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 728-980), 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 728-983), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 728-984), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-981), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-984), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - PB -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs (PA 72-980), 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - PB -- FY 1972 Office Expenses (PA 72-984), 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - PB -- FY 1972 Program Management Costs, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1973 General Management Costs (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ADMIN/OVP -- FY 1973 General Management Costs (PA 737-0980), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - ADMIN/OVP -- FY 1973 General Management Costs (PA 737-0981), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - ADMIN/OVP -- FY 1973 General Management Costs (PA 737-0982), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1973 General Management Costs -- St. Louis Office (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - E and R -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - E and R -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-982), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - E and R -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-984), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - E and R/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Education and Research/Public Policy and Social Organization (E and R/PPSO) -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-980), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - E and R/PPSO -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-982), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - E and R/PPSO -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-984), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - E and R/PPSO -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - FINANCE -- FY 1973 Investment Management Budget (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - FINANCE/OVP -- FY 1973 Investment Budget -- Representational and Administrative Staff (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - FINANCE/OVP -- FY 1983 Investment Management Budget -- Consultants (PA 73-982), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - HA -- FY 1973 Representational and Administrative Staff (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - HA -- FY 1973 Program Advisory Staff (PA 73-981), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - HA -- FY 1973 Consultants (PA 73-982), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - HA -- FY 1973 Office Expenses (PA 73-984), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - HA -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1973 Representational and Administrative Staff (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1973 Program Advisory Staff (PA 73-981), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1973 Training Associates (PA 73-983), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1973 Office Expenses (PA 73-984), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1973 Logistic Support -- Program Management Staff (PA 73-985), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1973 Representational and Administrative Staff (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1973 Program Advisory Staff (PA 73-981), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1973 Training Associates (PA 73-983), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1973 Office Expenses (PA 73-984), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1973 Logistic Support -- Program Management Staff (PA 73-985), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 738-0980), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 738-0981), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 738-0982), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1973 Consultants (PA 73-982, 738-0982, POP-IR5), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-980), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-982), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-984), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-981), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-982), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-984), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 739-980), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 739-982), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 739-983), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 739-984), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NA/RE -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-982), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-984), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-982), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (PA 73-984), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - PB -- FY 1973 Representational and Administrative Staff (PA 73-980), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - PB -- FY 1973 Program Advisory Staff (PA 73-981), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - PB -- FY 1973 Consultants (PA 73-982), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - PB -- FY 1973 Office Expenses (PA 73-984), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - PB -- FY 1973 Program Management Costs, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - ADMIN and FINANCE -- FY 1974 General Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - ADMIN, OP, OR and OSGC -- FY 1974 General Management Costs, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - ADMIN/OVP -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - E and R -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - E and R and USIAP -- FY 1974 Travel and Study Awards, 1974-1984 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - FINANCE -- FY 1974 Financial Management Costs, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - HA -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - HA -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1974 Logistic Support (Project Staff) and Small Program Actions, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 748-0984, PA 74-984), 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1974 Admin -- Karen Wilhelm Correspondence Re: Population Office Mailings (PA 74-984) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (PA 74-984, MCA 748-0984), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NA -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, for Support to MCAs, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, for Support to MCAs, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, for Support of MCAs, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - PB -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - PB -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - RE --FY 1974 Program Management Costs (MCA 74-980), 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - RE -- FY 1974 Program Management Costs, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1975 Special Retrenchment Fund (MCA 759-980), 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1975 Special Retrenchment Fund (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - ADMIN and FINANCE -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs (MCA 759-980), 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - ADMIN, OP, OR and OSGC -- FY 1975 General Management Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - E and R -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Education and Research/Public Education (E and R/PE) -- FY 1975-FY 1976 Travel and Study Awards -- DAPs, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - FINANCE -- FY 1975 Financial Management Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - HA -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - HA and OA -- FY 1975 Travel and Study Awards, Small Program Actions, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs (PA 75-980), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1975-FY 1977 Logistic Support (Project Staff) and Small Program Actions -- DAPs, 1974-1984 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1975 Small Program Actions -- DAPs, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs (PA 758-980), 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1975 Attachment File -- Office for Colombia and Venezuela FY 1975 Annual Report (PA 758-980), 1975 December (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1975 Logistic Support (Project Staff) and Small Program Actions, 1974-1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Logistic Support (Project Staff) and Small Program Actions, 1974-1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Attachment File -- Allan Gall Consultancy Reports (PA 75-980) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Attachment File -- Ralph Campbell Consultancy Memos (1 of 2) (PA 75-980), 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Attachment File -- Ralph Campbell Consultancy Report (2 of 2) (PA 75-980), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Attachment File -- Robert W. Kerwin Consultancy (PA 75-980, MEA-IR5), 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Lagos -- Gaston V. Rimlinger Consultancy Reports (1 of 2) (MCA 758-0980-243), 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Lagos -- Gaston V. Rimlinger Consultancy Reports (2 of 2) (MCA 758-0980-243) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Nairobi -- Herbert C. Kriesel Consultancy Memos (PA 75-980, MCA 758-0980-241), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1975 Tunis -- Maurice Harari Consultancy Report (PA 75-980, MCA 758-0980-244) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs (MCA 759-980), 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1975 Small Program Actions -- DAPs, 1974-1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1975 Correspondence Re: Terminology Used by FF in Reporting its Population Assistance Activities (PA 75-984) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - NA -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs (MCA 75-980), 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1975-FY 1977 Travel and Study Awards -- DAPs, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1975-FY 1977 Travel and Study Awards -- DAPs, 1974-1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NA/SD -- FY 1975-FY 1977 Travel and Study Awards -- DAPs, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1975-FY 1977 Travel and Study Awards -- DAPs, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - PB -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Resources and the Environment (RE) -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs (PA 758-980), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - RE -- FY 1975 Program Management Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - RE -- FY 1975-FY 1977 Travel and Study Awards -- DAPs, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1976 General Management Costs (MCA 76-980), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - ADMIN, OP, OR and OSGC -- FY 1976 General Management Costs, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - E and R -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - E and R -- FY 1976 Administrative File (MCA 76-980), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - FINANCE -- FY 1976 Financial Management Costs (MCA 76-980) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980, MCA 76-980), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1976 Quarterly Budget Projections by Field Office (PA 76-980), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1976 Memos Re: Annually Funded DAPs, Change in Cost Centers, etc. (PA 76-980), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1976 Mid-Year Budget Reviews for Program Management Costs (PA 76-980), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 Lagos -- Carl E. Taylor Consultancy Reports (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980-243) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 Lagos -- Elliot Berg Consultancy Report (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980-243) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 Lagos -- Gary Cziko Consultancy Report (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980-243) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 Lagos -- Jeanne S. Newman Consultancy Reports (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 New York -- Stephen R. Lewis, Jr. Consultancy Memos (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 Tunis -- Badi G. Foster Consultancy Report (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980-244) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1976 Tunis -- J. Eugene Poirier Consultancy Report (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980-244) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (MCA 76-980), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980, MCA 768-0980), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - NA -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs ( MCA 76-980), 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - NA/GL -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NA/OVP -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)